(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-08-06T22:10:57.862363",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
コンサートグッズ2次販売
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
コンサートは間もなく開始いたします。
The concert will be starting soon.
来場者の皆様へ
Attention For Visitors
コンサートグッズ2次販売
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
The concert will be starting soon.
Attention For Visitors
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
The concert will be starting soon.
Attention For Visitors
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
開演までしばらくお待ちください。
The concert will be starting soon.
ご来場にあたっての注意事項
[Attention For Visitors]
公演グッズ第2次販売
[2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales]
開演までしばらくお待ちください。
The concert will be starting soon.
Attention For Visitors
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
開演までしばらくお待ちください。
The concert will be starting soon.
Attention For Visitors
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
開演までしばらくお待ちください。
The concert will be starting soon.
Attention For Visitors
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
開演までしばらくお待ちください。
The concert will be starting soon.
Attention For Visitors
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
The concert will be starting soon.
開演までしばらくお待ちください。
Please wait a moment for the performance to begin.
Attention For Visitors
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
The concert will be starting soon. / 開演まで、しばらくお待ちください。
The concert will be starting soon. / Please wait a moment until the show begins.
Attention For Visitors
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
The concert will be starting soon. / 開演まで、しばらくお待ちください。
The concert will be starting soon. / Please wait a moment until the show begins.
Attention For Visitors
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
Kikiriki!
Thank you all so much for coming to Takanashi Kiara
and Ninomae Ina'nis's first concert, Day 2, Drawn to Dawn!
I am Takanashi Kiara, and next to me is...
Wah!
Good morning, afternoon, evening, everyone!
This is Numi Inami! Woo!
That's right, it is finally time to start Day 2!
Is everyone hyped? Yes!
Hype, hype, hype, hype, hype!
All right, before we kick things off, of course, we have some important safety rules and house guidelines to go over.
First, photography and the use of recording equipment are strictly prohibited during the performance.
However, if you are watching from home, screenshots are allowed. Please take lots of screenshots!
Yeah! スクショはオッケーですよ！
Yeah! Screenshots are okay!
Also, the venue is smoke-free, so please refrain from smoking inside.
Unless you're smoking hot like me!
Where have I heard that one before?
If you start unf- feeling unwell at- unf- feeling well... unfeeling well?
If you start feeling unwell at any point, please don't push yourself. Just reach out to the nearest staff member for help...
...and drink water.
For everyone's safety, please avoid any dangerous or disruptive behavior.
This once again, no matter how hype it is, includes moshing, diving...
...sitting on shoulders, jumping excessively, or throwing objects toward the stage. Climbing onto the stage, intentionally blocking the aisles, or rushing toward the front is also not allowed.
Please refrain from disruptive shouting, erratic lightstick movements, or any extreme motions that might interfere with the experience of those around you. Be considerate.
If you don't follow the instructions of our staff or the venue staff, you may be asked to leave the venue.
Yeah, please keep in mind that the venue, organizers, performers, and staff cannot be held responsible for any accidents, equipment damage, or trouble...
...blah-blah-blah... caused by failing to follow instructions. Suddenly stumbled over the same words.
It's hard, okay? I'm trying my best here! I can't read!
Additionally, any costs for damage resulting from ignoring these rules will be the responsibility of the person involved.
There are cameras in the venue for filming and photography today, and you might appear in the footage or photos. These may be used for promotional purposes later on, so please keep that in mind.
And finally, just like yesterday, the concert will be in two parts. There's a part for Wawa, and there's a part for me, so please look forward to both of them!
And yeah, that is it for the rules. Woo-hoo!
The show is about to begin, so get ready!
Have fun!
See you soon, bye-bye!
Bye-bye!
DRAWN TO DAWN
TAKANASHI KIARA / NINOMAE INA'NIS 1ST CONCERT
enlightened by the powers that be
the ruler of a world run on insanity
it's clear to me they still can't see
i'm just a normal girl
empowered by the ancient one's call
we're gonna be punstoppable, we're not a cult
nonsensical and nautical adventures lie in wait!!
gimme a one eight!!
Gimme a 1-8!!
ichi! hachi! takodachi!
ina ina ina
ina ina
ichi! hachi! takodachi!
ina ina ina, ina ina
sing with me!
俺のイナの世界線
To protect my Ina world line,
守るためにタコになろう！！
I'll become a Tako!!
ichi! hachi! takodachi!
ina ina ina, ina ina
いいタコになりますように
I hope to become a good Tako,
inasanityで踊りましょう！
let's dance in Inasanity!
think of all that you could be...
we're talking evolution, leave it all to me!
maybe just a touch of purple ink...
what'cha think?
it's a song you can't ignore
the ancient ones are calling you to be so much more!
just put your hand in mine and be reborn...
in a blink!
tell me what those legs are for?
俺のイナ運ぶためです！
They're for carrying my Ina!
you could use 6 more!
You could use six more!
感謝感謝！！ありがたい！！！
Gratitude, gratitude!! We are so grateful!!!
we could all get matching ears!
they aren't really ears though...
sleepy eyes to fight your fears!
例えばイナいないの世界！！！
For example, a world without Ina!!!
alright, listen to my song, am i striking a chord with you?
stringing you along, so don't let me get bored of you!
80 million strong and we've still got some more to do
Eighty million strong and we've still got some more to do.
everybody shout! world domination!!!
can i bank on your emotion? do i have you invested?
i don't wanna hear you say that you're not in-ate-rested!
your unwavering devotion isn't all i've requested
do you care? are you aware that you're dearest creations?!
Do you care? Are you aware that you're my dearest creations?!
oya oya! a cute little takodachi found its way here.
experimentation might be necessary...
takos.... we have to cook!!
いいタコだちの作り方！
How to make a good Takodachi!
ひっくり返して丸くして
Flip it over, make it round...
コロコロまわして焦がさずに
Roll it around without burning,
そっとカリッと中フワフワ
crispy on the outside, fluffy on the inside.
できたらソースでさあいただき！
Once it's done, add sauce and bon appétit!
enlightened by the powers that be
the ruler of a world run on insanity
it's clear to me they still can't see
i'm just a normal girl
empowered by the ancient one's call
we're gonna be punstoppable, we're not a cult
nonsensical and nautical adventures lie in wait
let's talk about the future to be
rewriting all of history in urgency
with cookies as our currency,
this place can finally heal!
insubordination won't fly
or else i'm making takoyaki tabehoudai
or else I'm making takoyaki all-you-can-eat.
no doubt about it, scream and shout it
welcome to my world!
ichi! hachi! takodachi!
ina ina ina ina
ina ina
俺のイナの世界線
My Ina timeline,
守るためにタコになろう！！
let's become a tako to protect it!!
so, it all goes back to eight and one
it's only world domination, and we've just begun
ah, what a place of never ending fun!
i want the world dyed in violet before i'm done!
so, it all goes back to eight and one
it's only world domination, and we've just begun
ah, what a place of never ending fun!
i want the world dyed in violet before i'm done!
so, it all goes back to eight and one
it's only world domination, and we've just begun
ah, what a place of never ending fun!
i want the world dyed in violet before i'm done!
私だけのもの そう私だけのもの
It's mine, yes, it belongs only to me.
千の黄金 数百年の財宝
Thousands of gold pieces, centuries of treasure,
この船に眠る
sleeping within this ship.
Hey everyone! Get ready to rock Day 2! Are you ready?!
古びた伝説は
The old legend,
呪われた幽霊船に
on the cursed ghost ship...
続く夜の航路
A night voyage that continues.
そこに何が残る
What remains there?
海賊の夢があるのなら
If there is a pirate's dream,
ただじゃ帰さないでしょう
I won't let you leave empty-handed.
うねる赤は
The surging crimson
若き熱のよう
is like youthful heat.
命を以て
With my life,
航海を理解させてやろう
I'll make you understand this voyage,
止まない
with unceasing
雨 of 弾丸で
bullets of rain.
狂おしいほど
Madly enough
この瞳焦がす
to burn these eyes,
生命の炎
the flame of life,
朱の色彩
a vermilion hue.
払う
To pay...
代償があるのなら
if there is a price to pay.
私だけのもの そう私だけのもの
It's mine, yes, it belongs only to me.
奪ってみろ
Try and steal
命の証を
the proof of my life.
あなたの求める
Everything
全てを
that you seek.
輝くは
What glitters
すべて錆びついて
will all rust away,
それでもなお
but even so,,
手に入れたいなら
if you still want it,
泡沫とともに
along with the bubbles,
沈め
sink down!
暗い深海に蓄える
Stored in the dark abyss,
億兆の財宝の行方
the whereabouts of trillions of treasures.
３、２、１で笑う
Laugh on three, two, one.
満月の金銀七宝
Gold, silver, and cloisonné under the full moon,
七つの海の極に
at the ends of the seven seas,
宝を見る者
those who look upon the treasure...
欲深い瞳を狙う
Targeting greedy eyes,
愚か者よ あの一矢放つ
you fools, I'll shoot that single arrow,
容赦なく沈むのを
to ruthlessly sink you down.
胸に刺さる
Piercing the chest,
黒い魂の群れ
a crowd of black souls.
影の底で
At the bottom of the shadows,
忍び寄る奈落の渦
the creeping vortex of the abyss.
まるで
Just like
タロットが示すよう
what the Tarot cards foretell.
手放したいなら
If you want to let go,
諦めたいなら
if you want to give up,
悪夢の中から
from this nightmare,
逃げられるのなら
if you can escape...
まだ掴んでる
You are still grasping onto it,
欲が重いから
because your greed is too heavy.
私だけのもの
It's mine,
そう私だけのもの
yes, it belongs only to me.
慎み深さを信じ込ませて縛って
Making me believe in modesty, binding me,
縛り付けて
tying me down.
だって気付いた
Because I realized...
海の出口
the exit from the sea.
永遠の揺らめきに
In the eternal shimmering...
...連れ出す船よ
...The ship that carries me out,
出航して
Set sail...
私のもの また私のもの
Mine, once again, mine...
積んで上ろう 打ち果てたとしても
I will pile them up and ascend, even if I am destroyed...
枯れない魂までは
...until my undying soul.
惑い 憂い 永遠の美貌
Confusion, grief, eternal beauty...
そんな幻 そうだっていいでしょう
Such illusions... that is fine, is it not?
手放して 翼ついたから
Since I let go and grew wings,
最高 夜明けに舵向けて
it is wonderful. Steer towards the dawn!
曰くを宿した船
The ship laden with pretexts,
希望だけ残していく
leaves behind only hope.
神は戻らないから
Since God will not return...
風に吹かれて
Blown by the wind,
誰も気づかぬよう
so that no one notices,
区別がつかない保存
unable to tell them apart
モノクロの世界保存
in this monochrome world.
色を足しても
Even if I add colors,
何も見えなくて
I can't see anything,
まるで私は保存
as if I was...
息を止めていた
...holding my breath.
もういいよ 遠くても
It's okay now, even if it's far away,
叶えたい 私は
I want to make it come true.
この闇の世界保存
In this dark world,
想いも抱きしめていたいのに
even though I want to hold my feelings close.
夢のキャンバスに
On the canvas of dreams,
描き続ける意味は
the meaning of continuing to paint
この胸に 輝いている
is shining in this heart of mine,
ストーリー
...as a story.
怯えることに
Fearing things
意味などないけれど
has no meaning, but...
拾い集めた保存
...as I gather
欠片 失うの保存
the pieces, I lose them.
そして夜は保存
And the night...
その冷たさを保存
...melts away
溶かして手を伸ばした
its coldness as I reach out.
もういいよ 遠くても
It's okay now, even if it's far away,
届けたい 私は
I want to reach you.
駆け抜けていく保存
I will run through,
涙も抱きしめていたいのに
even though I want to hold my tears close.
夢のキャンバスに
On the canvas of dreams,
心 込めるのは
pouring my heart in
この空に保存
is because I'll draw
描き出していく ストーリー
a story onto this sky.
そして夜は保存
And the night...
その冷たさを保存
...melts away
溶かして手を伸ばした
its coldness as I reach out.
もういいの 遠くても
It's okay, even if it's far away,
叶えたい 私の
I want to make it come true.
超えぬ世界保存
My unpassable world...
想いも言葉で包んだ
...I wrapped my feelings in words.
夢のキャンバスに
On the canvas of dreams,
色を足していく
I will add more color.
この胸に保存
In this chest,
今輝いて保存
shining right now.
強くなくてもいい
It's okay not to be strong,
壊れかけてもいい
it's okay to be broken.
この心は大空に羽ばたいて
This heart will flap its wings into the sky,
響くように
so that it resonates,
塗り替えていく パレット
repainting the palette.
Wow!
Hello everyone!
It is Day 2 of Connect the World!
Yes, yes. Welcome to Day 2 of Takanashi Kiara and Ninomae Ina'nis's first concert, Connect the World.
Are you guys enjoying the show so far?
Yay!
Ah... you know, um, I was really...
I want to talk about Taco-Tacover first because...
...yesterday, I heard you guys
sing along to the instrumental.
And I was like, "Uh, ah...
...I feel bad for those on Day 1."
But, you know, I knew I was opening for, you know, Day 2,
so I kind of thought of
a better song to open than Taco-Tacover, so...
Hope you guys had fun singing it!
Thank you again!
And of course,
I sang two of my senpais' songs.
Um, Senchou's "Dead Man's Chest"
and Towa-senpai's "Palette".
Um, I specifi-
I specifically wanted to...
...choose, um, their songs because, um,
they're, you know, senpais that I really look up to.
And, I always feel like, my journey here
wouldn't have been possible if I didn't discover my senpais...
...many, many years ago.
And I always, you know, wanted to pay respect
to the path they paved for us, so...
Yeah, I hope you guys enjoyed it.
I'm so nervous again.
Yeah, and, um, you know,
I of course didn't really tell you guys...
...specifically what penlight colors to use,
but I knew you guys would get my message...
...cause we share a brain cell, right, right?
And yeah, so, well, um,
now going by the different setlist because we...
...you know, have different setlist
for Day 1 and Day 2, so, uh...
...you know, going by the process of elimination,
we have a couple of songs from my new EP.
Let's actually...
who here bought my EP?
Yay! Thank you so much!
I hope you were lucky to get an autograph.
I tried to sign as much as possible,
but... I knew, you know, sometimes you can't be lucky.
Thank you, thank you!
But yeah, I want you guys to have...
...even more fun than before today.
I mean, you always have fun, so that's good, but, um, yeah!
And, you know, sing along, have fun!
And, I always think that...
...a live stage is where not only me
performing is creating the performance...
...but you guys as well. You really help...
...you know, help everyone
with that special experience, so...
...let's create an unforgettable
memory together today, okay?
Yay! Anyways...
...um, I would also like to shout-out
to those watching at home...
...and at the live viewing in the cinema,
hello, hello to you again! And also...
...the lovely, lovely girls
doing a watch-along right now. Hi, guys!
Thank you, ID, EN, and everyone else
doing the watch-along. Thank you, thank you!
Um, you know, um, I'm always
amazed by everyone's support.
Um, and, and really, without the support of...
...holoEN members as well, like, I wouldn't
have had the confidence to stand here today.
Thank you, I love you!
And of course, I would like to
remind you guys about the hashtag...
...for today's concert as well,
#TakoToriFirstConcert. As usual...
...post your thoughts about it,
post the screenshots, no videos, no videos!
Post the screenshots and, you know, Kiara and I,
whenever we have time, we've been checking...
...the hashtag, and of course after as well,
I want to hear, um, what you guys thought about the live, so yeah!
Thank you, thank you!
And, unlike yesterday...
...first MC means I unfortunately have to...
...bid farewell to those watching
the sneak peek on YouTube. I'm sorry.
But if you want to keep the party going...
...head to the streaming site via the description,
or comment... I don't know where the comment is.
Yeah!
But I know that some of you guys
won't get a chance to see my new outfit...
...that I revealed yesterday. So, I thought...
...maybe I'll do something, um,
maybe you guys can help me transition...
...into the new costume here,
so that even those of you...
And YouTube chiramise can see!
And the YouTube preview can see!
All right, so I'm going to count down from three.
Count down with me, okay?
And then we'll switch into the new outfit for you guys to see.
Ready?
Ready? Give me a "wah" if you're ready!
All right, all right, all right. Here we go!
Three, two, one... hya!
Tada!
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
All right, it's time to move on to the next song.
And I think this song also fits...
...the starry stage perfectly. Not- Not that one yet, but...
But this one is from one of my favorite franchises.
So I hope you guys listen. Anyways,
the song will fit the starry stage perfectly.
Please give it a listen.
無料パートは終了いたしました。ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The sneak peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching.
The free part has ended. Thank you for watching!